[Music]
Most of the tools aren't perfect. They
have their blind spots and they have
their things that they're really good at
and things that they're not so good at.
So, it's about creating workflows about
maybe chaining together two or three
tools that fill in the weak spots of
another one. Um so like I said earlier
Gemini is really good for being my
architect and creating the big
understand the bigger picture the full
context of the code base uh is going to
handle such a large context that wind
surf and poured me underneath the hood
uh to go and execute on this plan that
Gemini
um kind of see yeah testing out the
different LLM and the different tools
and the thing is there's like limitless
combinations of this now so it's not the
easiest thing but finding one that works
for your workload because every
developer kind of builds very very
differently
As somebody who would be try to become
an AI test developer, do you recognize
two or three pitfalls that you think
they try, you know, they should be wary
of?
>> This is probably something that I do is
try out every single tool and get lost
in every single rabbit hole. But a lot
of it is noise. Things are not sticking
around, especially with how fast the
area is moving.
>> Really,
>> um, some news that comes out this week
could no longer be relevant in a month.
So, I'd say if you have limited time and
most people do your work in a job and
there's only so much time you can
dedicate outside of your actual role to
learning this stuff,
>> um it's kind of the big beats that um
are repeated again and again like uh in
media whether your your social media
choice is Twitter or YouTube or discord
um there things that get repeated again.
Code is big curses. So, when curs was
popular, it was the thing that everyone
was talking about. Same thing with wind
surf and board coat. And I think going
by by crowds because you can't really do
this alone, keep up with it. I think
generally that's a good rule of thumb to
to go with a good choice
>> um of of tooling.
>> Where do you see yourself in building
that company? Like uh how would you rate
your AI's adoption? Uh yeah, keen to to
get some cover.
We
founded sort of eight months ago. So,
you know, at that point, cursive was a
thing.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, we were already on like the Claude 4
level models.
>> Um, so yeah, we were really sort of
founded in the like very recently. Um,
and as such, like I guess since the sort
of first day of the company, we've been
using frontier models. Um, but I think
>> so from day one, you're AI native
>> from day one. But I think the surprising
thing is like almost how little we use
AI as in like depends on what your
perspective is but all of our code goes
through editors like person um and we
use it to to augment our uh development
processes. We build a lot of our dev
tools with AI and run them. But besides
that and also help around
planning, structuring, emailing and
things like that like there is still
quite a lot of manual processes within
the company and I think that's quite
surprising to people because people in
legacy companies understand that things
are very manual. People think that
Frontier
startups coming out of for example Y
Cominator are just entirely automated.
And there are some companies in my in
like in my batch and in um in in you
know batches around our company that are
doing sort of multiple millions of
dollars with like a couple of people at
the company. They are
>> um managing to do more with less. But I
think it's like it's not quite what
people think it is right now, which is
that you just have fully autonomous
agents running around doing integral
parts of the company. It's more like
people are being augmented and able to
output more. But there are still these
sort of annoyances and and human parts
of the company. So I I don't think
necessarily we are where we should be as
a company like that could be fully
autonomous agents that go and do things
for us. Um, are you doing this more as a
guard rail or as a necessity?
So, are you injecting that human in the
loop because you care about security and
care about reliability or it's because
it's actually not even possible just yet
to have it fully autonomous? I think
because
we our role I think as humans now as as
engineers people running companies is to
inject the taste and so
I don't just want to let us spit out
garbage kabood
>> I want it to because it can it can it
can output millions of tokens very
quickly right and not all of that is
high quality so I want to inject my
taste on top of what the model outputs
and steer it.
>> Here we're building the AI native devs.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh it's a repository of tools,
>> open source, private, whatnot that try
to essentially
repertoire everything into one big
mapping
>> and also try to fix that or like be part
of the solution of like there's so much
happening, there's so much noise,
>> how do you make sense of this noise? Um,
how do you approach actually all these
emerging tools and how how do you pick
them as a CTO?
>> Sure. I think word of mouth is huge.
>> We look at companies that we respect and
we see what software they use. And so
that's how we came across Linear for
example. That's how we came across
Mintify.
>> Yeah.
>> Um,
>> and these other core components that
make up our stack. So word of mouth, if
you're in the startup ecosystem, look at
the high performance and see what
they're using. and generally they're
using like you know high quality
software. So word of mouth is is more
important than ever I think
>> in terms of like keeping up with the
field as a whole like outside of like
individual SAS products just keeping up
with the field. There's a newsletter
that I listen to or I I I read that on
don't worry about the vase by a guy in
Moshvitz and he's a speaker on a
commentator on the AI landscape and he's
incredibly assume and incredibly
observant and intelligent and says very
smart things about where we're headed um
and talks about recent events, what
models were released, what the
difference was as important. So I'm
keeping up the landscape just a number
of models that are being released and
changes in you know in the in the
landscape that that's where I go to
don't worry about the bars.
>> What do you find frustrating as an AI
native?
>> Essentially I think the biggest
frustration right now is that AI is used
so drastically by everyone. So it's very
difficult to find someone who uses AI
for the good. For example, confident
coder would know exactly what kind of
component component they want to
generate using AI and they have already
you know loads of experience to work on.
So all they do is that they integrate
the new generated component in the
previous workflows. But when someone new
is coming to the market all they do is
that whiteboard. So I think that
whiteboarding tool even bold has like
generated so many followers. It's an
amazing tool but I think it falls behind
in terms of the quality of its customer.
So I think as long as people are aware
that AI is supposed to make you better
not you don't have to rely on AI that
will be much you know easier.
>> What's a obscure tool you like in the AI
realm? Obscure tool.
>> Yeah.
>> I'll tell you one thing after seeing
Tesla's demo today right
>> it really gave me uh a new tool to think
about and play about with to be honest.
Still very new to it. Only started with
it today. I'm grateful that I got um
early access or closed beta access and I
was speaking to a couple of my
colleagues today of the team and I was
just like this tool is amazing like I'm
going to see if I can get you access as
well and we can play about with it a
little bit.
>> How mature would you say the adoption of
AI is at your current firm?
>> I would say say it's still in the early
stages. We are still in the process of
trying to prove to the business the
benefits
>> that AI can bring. Um we have a AI
working group which uh we're working
with. Um and it's also about the wider
non-technical audience to give them the
understanding of the overall value and
how it can help the performance of uh
the organization.
>> Are there metrics that you use to prove
to enterprises the value of AI?
>> We are still trying to build that first
through proof of concepts before we can
even get to the metrics. Um it's about
showing
uh different data sets what we can
achieve from those data sets through the
use of AI and then we can put metrics on
top of it.
>> As an AI developer, what's currently
something that you find is misunderstood
in our space? We're trying to build
these AI workflows using graphs, trying
to model them as kind of graphs of
prompts calling each other and langraph
being the canon canonical example here.
A lot of the community has coalesed
around that.
But I find that that approach is very
restrictive and very limiting. It
doesn't help to build durable AI
workflows that work effectively, handle
failure effectively
due to network hiccups or servers
crashing or network partitions or what
have you. And it doesn't work well with
managing deployments as well because if
you have a multi- aent system as
Entropic recently noted, you need
something like Rainbow Deployments in
order to actually be able to deploy a
change to the system in the middle of it
running some complex workflows
>> so that the existing workflows continue
on the existing code, but new workflows
are now working with the new code. And I
think more and more we're going to see
these kinds of distributed systems
engineering challenges
>> being presented to us.
[Music]
[Applause]